highrises.com 2018-11-18

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Service

At Highrises.com, we recognize that you expect privacy and security when it comes to information that personally identifies you and allows you to be individually contacted (”Personal Information”). Highrises.com has adopted the following online privacy policy because we understand the need to safeguard the information you may be providing to us at our web site. We collect and retain information about you only when we believe it will help us provide you with the services and products that you desire.

### Personalized Home Search Registration

When you sign up for our personalized home search, we may use that information to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our web site, new products or services, and special offers we think you’ll find valuable.  We may also use the information to refer you to brokers in your market that are affiliated with Highrises.com.

### Online Forms

When you request other information from us through our various order forms, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address and telephone numbers so we can be sure to get in touch with you when and how you ask us to. The information we receive from you is protected against unauthorized access once we receive it. We limit access to your information to employees who have a business reason for accessing it. We also educate our employees about the importance of your privacy through our educational programs and company policies.

### About Our Cookies

Our site uses cookies dropped by third parties to track how you use the site and target ads to you on other websites.  Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer hard drive. Our cookies allow us to welcome you back to our site and provide you with your personalized home searches. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser to prevent cookies from being placed on your computer without your consent. You can still use our regular home search feature and every other function on our site even though your computer will not accept cookies. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to discover your identity and we do not know your identity unless you tell us.

If you would like to opt out of receiving targeted advertising, please visit the DAA ([www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)) and follow the instructions on the Consumer Choice Page to opt out.

### Links to other web sites

Our web site contains links to and from other web sites and may be in the form of display advertising. We cannot guarantee that web sites other than Highrises.com will respect and protect your Personal Information in the same manner that we do. We urge you to go to and read the Privacy Statements of other web sites when you visit them for your own protection. We also are not responsible for the content of web sites other than Highrises.com

### Referrals

When you provide us with Personal Information such as your name, email and/or phone number, you authorize Highrises.com to refer you to our partner real estate brokerage and/or Referral Exchange and/or a mortgage broker in the market in which you registered or inquired.  You also acknowledge that Highrises.com may be paid a valuable consideration for facilitating such a referral.

### Your Consent

When you provide us with Personal Information, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Highrises.com.  This includes phone calls, emails and text notifications by us and/or our partner agents. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.  Should you wish to discontinue the communications from Highrises.com, simply notify us that you wish to opt out.
